Takayasu Nasu

#112 1209 Jervis St Vancouver BC V6R2B6 / Tel: +1(604)376-2691 / E-mail: taka.beckham@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/TakayasuNasu / portfolio: https://www.i-nasu.com/ / App Store: https://apps.apple.com/us/app/queens-game/id1575671780

Profile

Senior Full-Stack Web Developer with more than 9 years of experience in Information Technology Industry. Experience In Requirements Definition, System Design, Development And Testing For Various Applications Like Client Server, Web Applications IOS Application, Android Application.

Skills

Java	• PHP	 JavaScript 	 TypeScript 	• Swift	Kotolin	 Python 	• Ruby
 HTML 	• CSS	 SCSS 	 React 	 Vue.js 	 Anguler.js 	 Node.js 	 JQuery
 Next.js 	 Wordpress 	 Laravel 	 CakePhp 	 Zend 	 Rails 	 Graphql 	 MySql
 SQLite 	 Apache 	 Nginx 	 Docker 	 Git/Github 	• AWS	 CircleCI 	

Work Experience

Lead Front End Developer (Contract) - DPCode Inc. / Vancouver, Canada (May 2021 - Present)

- · Mentoring members, managing tasks, One-on-one meetings, and reviewing their sources. My team has 6 people including me.
- Front end requirements definition, spec design, implementation.

Full Stack Developer / Technical Director - Medix inc. / Tokyo, Japan (June 2017 - August 2020)

- Created SPA for centralized management which useful knowledge within the company that was stored in various locations. That SPA is made with Docker,
 Laravel. Graphal and Vue.is.
- As project leader, I selected technologies and supported members of the project team.
- Built a Staging environment and set a deployment system using Github webhook.
- Worked closely with other developers and UI designers in an agile environment.

Senior Web Developer - Strawbag inc. / Tokyo, Japan (November 2014 - October 2016)

- Created a CI system that combined Bitbucket, Wercker, and Slack to support development when I built a job-search management site using the php Slim framework.
- Cooperated and built some web applications with the Chinese coworker. That's when I supported him by creating task management, specification
 explanations, sample code, and documentation.

Junior Web Developer - BTM inc. / Tokyo, Japan (April 2013 - October 2014)

- · Continued to release Smartphone game which over 100 php files, built with over 100 tables, used by over 10,000 people daily consistently.
- Created Android application that uses polymorphism in its design which is made with Java and I manage team tasks.

Junior Web Developer - I-Freek / Fukuoka, Japan (June 2012 - March 2013)

- Modified an existing program made with Perl and deploy it on Linux while checking the Apache conf file with Vim.
- Supported Android app which uses GPS made with Java using Eclipse.
- Wrote clean and stable code and accompanying documentation.

Projects

Dpcode Academy - https://dpcode.academy (May 2021 - Present)

- Tech Stack: React/Next.js/Cognito/Api Gateway/DynamoDB/scss
- · People who want to study computer science, algorithms, and something like that can sign up for online classes from this site.
- Students can know which lectures they have attended, and the instructor can control the content and duration of the lectures.

Queen's game (April 2021 ~ July 2021)

- App Store: https://apps.apple.com/us/app/queens-game/id1575671780
- Tech Stack: Swift/Realm/MVVM/RxSwift/Core Animations/Figma
- Queen's game is a party game which is kind of combination of "Simon Says" and "truth or dare."

Famus Spot Tour (December 2020 ~ March 2021)

- Tech Stack: Swift/Realm/SnapKit/Mapkit/Core Graphics/Core Animations/Firebase/Figma
- . An application that provides directions to people who don't know how to go there and introduces recommended spots to tourists who are new to Vancouver.
- Product manager, programmer, and UI designer working with my team members.

S-Portal (Jun 2019 - August 2020)

- Tech Stack: Vue/SPA/Graphql/Laravel/Docker
- SPA for centralized management of knowledge related to site production, accessed daily by 80% of all employees

FeedLP (January 2018 - September 2019) - https://www.itstaffing.jp/lp/fd002/?mfeed=D210100838D

- Tech Stack: React/Go/AWS Fargate/Docker/MySql
- We made an API for the job information used in the feed ads and used React to display it dynamically. The UI is now ready to be updated without any work
 on the server-side.

Landing Page and Wordpress (Occasionally 4 to 5 site per year)

- Tech Stack: html/css(scss)/JQery/Vue.js/php
- Perfect coding using css grid and flex-box based on the design data (psd) to improve conversion rates.
- https://www.iprimo.jp/ | https://www.exchangeuse.com/ | https://www.nichiiweb.jp/kaji/

Web browser Social game applications (January 2014 - October 2014)

- Tech Stack: php/Smarty/MySql/JavaScript/Jira
- · Continued to release Smartphone game which over 100 php files, built with over 100 tables, used by over 10,000 people daily consistently.

Education